<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Recent Content on  </title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/index.xml</link>
    
    
    
    <updated>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;fanatical jacket winner&#34; src=&#34;//drops.albush.com/fanjackettrans.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I help connect people with the information they need to make awesome things in the cloud. I enjoy creating new teams. I&amp;rsquo;m currently building the Technical Community Manager team at Rackspace. I also was a founding member &amp;amp; architect of Rackspace&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Launch Team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During my time on the Launch Team, I helped more than 100 new cloud consumers get started with cloud hosting, developed a weekly live video show - &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.rackspace.com/p/officehours&#34;&gt;Office Hours Hangouts&lt;/a&gt;, was one of the first 175 Rackers to become certified &amp;ldquo;Cloud Savvy,&amp;rdquo; and was awarded the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iOxGVJ3Zv94&#34;&gt;Fanatical Jacket, Rackspace&amp;rsquo;s highest honor&lt;/a&gt; for outstanding customer support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before Rackspace, I helped create the Stevie Award winning onboarding program for cloud collaboration suite Central Desktop, where I worked directly with companies and organizations like MLB.com, Sesame Workshop, and IEEE. When I&amp;rsquo;m not helping customers learn how to build awesome things in the cloud, I can be found performing improv comedy with &lt;a href=&#34;http://cszsa.com/&#34;&gt;ComedySportz San Antonio&lt;/a&gt;, or dreaming up new styles for my award-winning mustache.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Instagram Gratification</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/iftttinstagram.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/iftttinstagram.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;I want instant gratification. Especially on Twitter. It&amp;rsquo;s 140 characters short. Give me the info, and let me look at the next tweet. So when I see a tweet linking to Instagram, sometimes I don&amp;rsquo;t follow the link. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to wait an extra few seconds to open a new tab, wait for Instagram to load, look at the picture, then head back to Twitter. Especially on a mobile device. Especially because I don&amp;rsquo;t actually use Instagram and can&amp;rsquo;t find this content anywhere else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;There is a better way&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter If This Then That, a great service that uses &amp;ldquo;recipes&amp;rdquo; to run workflows, connecting apps together. Here&amp;rsquo;s one for you Instagram users to natively embed Instagram images into the Twitter timeline&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ifttt.com/view_embed_recipe/103249-post-your-instagram-pictures-as-native-twitter-pictures&#34; target = &#34;_blank&#34; class=&#34;embed_recipe embed_recipe-l_55&#34; id= &#34;embed_recipe-103249&#34;&gt;&lt;img src= &#39;https://ifttt.com/recipe_embed_img/103249&#39; alt=&#34;IFTTT Recipe: Post your Instagram pictures as native Twitter pictures connects instagram to twitter&#34; width=&#34;370px&#34; style=&#34;max-width:100%&#34;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async type=&#34;text/javascript&#34; src= &#34;//ifttt.com/assets/embed_recipe.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Performing with San Antonio ComedySportz</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/cszsa2014-11-15.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/cszsa2014-11-15.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The good news is I&amp;rsquo;m performing improv comedy on Saturday. The bad news is I don&amp;rsquo;t get to make stuff up with my friends as much as I would like. I think that&amp;rsquo;s just a fact of this stage of my life. I don&amp;rsquo;t have to like it, but there it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&#34;fb-root&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;script&gt;(function(d, s, id) { var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0]; if (d.getElementById(id)) return; js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id; js.src = &#34;//connect.facebook.net/en_US/all.js#xfbml=1&#34;; fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs); }(document, &#39;script&#39;, &#39;facebook-jssdk&#39;));&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;fb-post&#34; data-href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/CSzSA/photos/gm.1560060184209906/10152849754265763/?type=1&#34; data-width=&#34;466&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;fb-xfbml-parse-ignore&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/CSzSA/photos/gm.1560060184209906/10152849754265763/?type=1&#34;&gt;Post&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/CSzSA&#34;&gt;ComedySportz San Antonio&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started performing improv in High School. That&amp;rsquo;s over half a lifetime ago. We practiced or performed at least once a week then. In college, I performed as often as possible - not as much as I would like, but several times a month. The magical period between college and married with children was filled almost exclusively with improv. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to go back to the rest of that lifestyle, but I do miss the community of improvisors we built up during that time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommended Android Apps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/androidapps.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/androidapps.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;A friend just got her first Android phone, so I put together a quick list of apps I think are well worth an install. This is by no means a complete list, just a start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;All of the Google Apps. Most of them aren&amp;rsquo;t the default on a Samsung device, and it&amp;rsquo;s well worth it to either install them or set them up as your default.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.launcher&#34;&gt;Google Now Launcher&lt;/a&gt; - provides the default Google Android Experience - No Samsung/HTC crap interface.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.adm&#34;&gt;Android Device Manager&lt;/a&gt; - remotely manage your device. Locate it when it&amp;rsquo;s lost. Remote wipe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.paidtasks&#34;&gt;Google Opinion Rewards&lt;/a&gt; - Answer the occasional survey, get some change added to your Play account. Buy more games.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.inbox&#34;&gt;Inbox by Gmail&lt;/a&gt; - replacement for standard Gmail app. Allows you to quickly manage email, and take action on your mail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.music&#34;&gt;Google Play Music&lt;/a&gt; - Now with Songza integration. Great way to pick out music for whatever you&amp;rsquo;re doing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google+ - Just a fan, don&amp;rsquo;t mind me. But it comes with the Photos app, which has some great editing tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.android.chrome&#34;&gt;Chrome Browser&lt;/a&gt; - Don&amp;rsquo;t use the default browser. Just don&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Misc&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=spinninghead.carhome&#34;&gt;Car Home Ultra&lt;/a&gt; - Turns your phone into a dashboard while you drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.authy.authy&#34;&gt;Authy 2-Factor Authentication&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=mobi.beyondpod&#34;&gt;BeyondPod&lt;/a&gt; - Podcast catcher/player w/ beautiful design and variable speed playback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.pushbullet.android&#34;&gt;Pushbullet&lt;/a&gt; - Mirror selected notifications from your device to your computer. Great to see who&amp;rsquo;s calling, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.linkbubble.playstore&#34;&gt;Link Bubble Browser&lt;/a&gt; - Open links in a &amp;lsquo;bubble,&amp;rsquo; then open those bubbles individually. Prevents you from having to jump back and forth between apps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mcc.alarmclocklifetime&#34;&gt;Life Time Alarm Clock&lt;/a&gt; - A great alarm clock app. Easy to use, and works well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.lastpass.lpandroid&#34;&gt;LastPass&lt;/a&gt; - Keeps all of your passwords safe. Will copy/paste your passwords into new apps. Huge time saver.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Work&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mappedin.shuriken&#34;&gt;MappedIn&lt;/a&gt; - Internal Maps. My workplace is mapped here, and I can find my way around much better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ninefolders.hd3&#34;&gt;Nine&lt;/a&gt; - Exchange/Active Sync client. Holy crap, this is a great app. Easily worth the $10 price tag.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rsa.securidapp&#34;&gt;RSA Token&lt;/a&gt; - Instead of the key fob&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;Fun/Distraction/Just Plain Dumb Apps&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.richapps.hodorkeyboard.app&#34;&gt;Hodor Keyboard&lt;/a&gt; - Hodor! Hodor hodor, hodor; hodor hodor?! Hodor. Hodor hodor hodor hodor&amp;hellip; Hodor hodor hodor&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.imgur.mobile&#34;&gt;Imgur&lt;/a&gt; - Cats, gifs, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.photofy.android&#34;&gt;Photofy Photo Editing Collage&lt;/a&gt; - Make photo collages. Add words to them. Share them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Series</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/worldseries.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/worldseries.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was five years old when the Royals were last in the World Series. This year, they&amp;rsquo;re back again. Unlike other teams shutout from the World Series, the Royals haven&amp;rsquo;t even been to the postseason in 29 years. The won the title in 1985, and then went into a three decade slide. Some of us remained fans, others jumped to other teams and other sports - KC&amp;rsquo;s MLS franchise, Sporting KC, has won the only championship since the Royals won the World Series in &amp;lsquo;85. I stayed loyal as a way to keep connected to my friends and family in KC after I moved away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;img-responsive&#34; src=&#34;http://drops.albush.com/marshall85.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;img-responsive&#34; src=&#34;http://drops.albush.com/simon85.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My sons are 4 and 1, and sharing this post season with them has been one of the highlights of my life. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember much from the 1985 season, but I do remember how excited my dad was. Dad&amp;rsquo;s not here to celebrate this postseason with us, so I&amp;rsquo;m making sure I get to spend as much time with my boys as possible. They might not remember it, but I will.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SungWoo Lee Is Not A Lucky Charm, He&#39;s a Fan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/sungwoo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/sungwoo.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;background-color:#fff;display:inline-block;font-family:&#39;Helvetica Neue&#39;,Arial,sans-serif;color:#a7a7a7;font-size:11px;width:100%;max-width:594px;&#34;&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;overflow:hidden;position:relative;height:0;padding:67.508418% 0 0 0;width:100%;&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&#34;//embed.gettyimages.com/embed/453500438?et=DU8MVMI1SA98Ar1R9yr1EA&amp;similar=on&amp;sig=KDFbjwdEMUNcWUtp8XQQUmj2LIIT6N5CbWF2mT5m13w=&#34; width=&#34;594&#34; height=&#34;401&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;display:inline-block;position:absolute;top:0;left:0;width:100%;height:100%;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;margin:0;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;padding:0;margin:0 0 0 10px;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gettyimages.com/detail/453500438&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; style=&#34;color:#a7a7a7;text-decoration:none;font-weight:normal !important;border:none;display:inline-block;&#34;&gt;#453500438&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gettyimages.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; style=&#34;color:#a7a7a7;text-decoration:none;font-weight:normal !important;border:none;display:inline-block;&#34;&gt;gettyimages.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking at SungWoo Lee and only seeing a &amp;ldquo;Good Luck Charm,&amp;rdquo; you&amp;rsquo;re doing it wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don&amp;rsquo;t know who SungWoo Lee is, take a minute to read his story. (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ranyontheroyals.com/2014/08/to-sung-woo-thanks-for-everything-rany.html&#34;&gt;Rany Jazayerli has a perfect recap.&lt;/a&gt;)  SungWoo Lee isn&amp;rsquo;t a magical creature capable of making the Royals win. He&amp;rsquo;s not a good luck charm that can propel the Royals to victory in the World Series. He is a great guy that helped a franchise, their city, and their fans remember why they love the game, and this team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SungWoo reminded us what it&amp;rsquo;s like to be a fan. He&amp;rsquo;s full of excitement for this team. He loves the sport. His arrival in KC last August brought that excitement to a city that had all but lost their ability to get excited about the Royals. The Royals were chugging along on the verge of another medicare season - one with almost no possibility of seeing the postseason. And then SungWoo hit town, and things started to click for the Royals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baseball is a superstitious game. The players, the fans, they all have a tendency toward believing that random events are connected. &lt;strong&gt;Random Event 1&lt;/strong&gt;: The Royals start to warm up and play some great baseball. &lt;strong&gt;Random Event 2&lt;/strong&gt;: A kid from Korea shows up in Kansas City and catches a few games. In the mind of a KC Baseball fan, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to forever link those two events together. We all know that correlation does not prove causation, but after nearly 3 decades of abysmal baseball, we&amp;rsquo;ll take anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To say that SungWoo&amp;rsquo;s visit didn&amp;rsquo;t have a positive impact on the Royals, the city, and the fans would be to miss his biggest contribution: Fandom. He reminded us what it&amp;rsquo;s like to be an optimistic Royals fan. And I truly believe that message made it all the way to the players and management of the Kansas City Royals. What a great reminder for the team that they have fans all around the world. Fans who get up in the middle of the night to catch a game; Fans that could so easily have walked away from the Royals, jumped on the Yankees, Red Sox, or any other bandwagon out there; Fans that love and support the Royals, when frankly the Royals have done nothing in the last three decades to deserve that love. That&amp;rsquo;s a strong message, and the Royals received it and acted on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To take that experience, the lessons that the Royals, the Fans, and the City all learned from it, and to turn it into &amp;ldquo;SungWoo is a good luck charm&amp;rdquo; cheapens the entire experience. It&amp;rsquo;s not fair to SungWoo, who never wanted any of this celebrity. And it&amp;rsquo;s not fair to the team, that, in case you didn&amp;rsquo;t notice, made it to the postseason for the first time in 29 years and then preceded to win 8 games in a row - All while SungWoo was half a planet away. The Royals are winning - they&amp;rsquo;ve found some #RoyalsDevilMagic or something. Whatever it is, they&amp;rsquo;re winning. And they&amp;rsquo;re winning without SungWoo in the stadium/city/time zone/country/hemisphere. Don&amp;rsquo;t take that away from the guys who have worked their asses off to achieve a record setting postseason performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not saying that we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be happy that SungWoo is coming back to KC. We should be happy &lt;em&gt;for&lt;/em&gt; SungWoo, not because we believe that his presence will further the Royals odds of winning it all. So if you&amp;rsquo;re lucky enough to see SungWoo at the stadium this week, thank him for his fandom. Thank him for his energy and enthusiasm. Thank him for reminding the rest of us how great it is to be a fan.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billy Butler Stole a Base</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/billystealssecond.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/billystealssecond.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;video-container&#34;&gt;
&lt;video controls loop&gt;
  &lt;source src=&#34;http://drops.albush.com/billystealssecond.mov&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34;&gt;
  Your browser does not support the video tag.
&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this happened. Crazy world we live in. Crazy world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://yacketylapse.com/&#34;&gt;yaketyfied via YaketyLapse, a silly idea from H. Wade Minter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minimizing the Impact of a Cloud Server Reboot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/reboots.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/reboots.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Last week at work, we had to reboot almost all of our Cloud servers. In anticipation of the reboots, my colleague Alison Oster and I wrote the following article for our customers. I think the advice is valid, regardless of where you host, so I&amp;rsquo;m reposting it here, and including the video hangout where we covered these tips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;video-container&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;390&#34; src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/m9kg26vTGB0?list=UUG0VI_ayS-I0RQpBna4Tisw&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Minimizing the Impact of a Cloud Server Reboot&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all try to prevent it, but from time to time you might find that your server needs to be rebooted. While the reboot is generally a fast process, it can sometimes present additional headaches. Fortunately, a little bit of  planning can prevent a lot of headache. Let&amp;rsquo;s go over a few tips to make sure that any server reboots are fast and minimally disruptive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Create a System Image for restoration and scaling&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A system image is a snapshot of your server at a given point in time. You can use an image to build a replacement server, or to create redundancy and scalability.&lt;br /&gt;
Images are intended to capture the relatively static operating system, installed packages and configurations - not the dynamic data on the server. For Performance Cloud Servers only the System partition is imaged, which is why we recommend pairing system images with a Cloud Backup regimen.&lt;br /&gt;
System images can be taken ad hoc, or on a recurring scheduled basis. Recurring images are given a retention policy which saves new images for a fixed number of days before being replaced by the newest image. We recommend at least 3 days of images at any time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information on Images see &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rackspace.com/knowledge_center/article/rackspace-cloud-backup-overview&#34;&gt;this Rackspace guide to creating and restoring from images&lt;/a&gt; and this &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rackspace.com/knowledge_center/article/backing-up-an-ms-sql-server-2008-database&#34;&gt; Rackspace FAQ on scheduled images&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Ensure server has backups configured and running.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We recommend everyone use backups to keep their data up-to-date. The Rackspace Cloud Backup product runs a differential backup on a set frequency. This backup can be set to run on any number of directories. It is also important to remember that on Performance Cloud Servers with a data disc the data partition is not included in any image snapshots taken. Make sure those data partitions are included in your backup scheme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For additional information on Cloud Backup, please review &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rackspace.com/knowledge_center/article/rackspace-cloud-backup-overview&#34;&gt;the Rackspace Cloud Backup Overview in their Knowledge Center&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For many Linux servers these directories will need to be backed up:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;/home&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;/root&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;/etc (This will contain most of your configuration files)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;/var/www (This will often contain your websites and files)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;/var/lib/mysqlbackup (Servers built using Rackspace Managed Operations will have an automated process that automatically runs a mysql dump to this folder.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Windows Servers we recommend you backup where your data might be stored, e.g.:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C:\inetpub&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C:\Users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any additional drives such D:, E: and so on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;MS-SQL Backup&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, Cloud Backup will not backup live databases. &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rackspace.com/knowledge_center/article/backing-up-an-ms-sql-server-2008-database&#34;&gt;Backup must be done through Microsoft SQL Server Management Studio&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course we recommend that you carefully consider your specific applications, and their backup needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For additional reading, see: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rackspace.com/knowledge_center/article/rackspace-cloud-backup-vs-cloud-server-image-backups&#34;&gt;notes on the differences between Cloud Backup and Image Snapshots.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_4&#34;&gt;Ensure services are configured to start after boot.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When installing a service it does not automatically configure this to start again once the server is rebooted.  However, there is an easy way to resolve this.  Below are some links on how to do this on RHEL/CentOS, Ubuntu and even Windows servers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rackspace.com/knowledge_center/article/centos-chkconfig&#34;&gt;How to use chkconfig with RHEL/CentOS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/f/25/t/4315&#34;&gt;How to use update-rc.d with Ubuntu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/windows/desktop/ms681957%28v=vs.85%29.aspx&#34;&gt;Automatically Starting Services with Windows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ensure IPtables/Windows Firewall rules are saved and configured to restart on reboot.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is important to ensure that the firewall rules that you have worked hard to configure stay active upon reboot.  Below are a couple of links on how to ensure that this is the case for both &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.centos.org/docs/5/html/5.1/Deployment_Guide/s2-basic-firewall-activate-iptables.html&#34;&gt;iptables&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/library/cc749262%28v=ws.10%29.aspx&#34;&gt;Windows Firewall.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SSL passphrase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We generally do not recommend using a passphrase when generating a SSL certificate.  If you do already have a passphrase in place for your SSL certificate however, you will need to input that into the server upon reboot.  The services on the server will not be able to start without first having to input that passphrase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ensure that Cloud Block Storage Volumes Attach on Reboot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have data on a Cloud Block Storage volume, you&amp;rsquo;ll want to make sure that any volumes are properly connected after a reboot. To ensure this, you need to add your volume to the static file system information in the fstab file. See &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rackspace.com/knowledge_center/article/prepare-your-cloud-block-storage-volume&#34;&gt;step 5 in this guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Windows users, mounted block storage should remain mounted after reboot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FSCK (File System Consistency Check)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&#34;/general/f/34/t/3756&#34;&gt;fsck&lt;/a&gt; generally runs automatically at boot time.  There are 2 common triggers for automatically executing a fsck.  Either the operating system detect that a file system is in an inconsistent state (likely due to a non graceful shutdown like crash or power loss) or after a certain number of times that the system is mounted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you reboot your server this fsck may happen automatically.  If it does, this could cause an increase in the delay for your server coming back online.  Delay&amp;rsquo;s are usually never good, but in this case the delay can save your server.  I would suggest just letting the fsck complete even though it may cause delays for you.  If you attempt to reboot the server again, it is just going to go right back into fsck which will only increase the delay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_5&#34;&gt;Test All The Things!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having images, backups, configurations, and redundancies in place are vital, but we strongly recommend taking a few minutes to test the entire process of getting your environment back up and running, so that you know how your servers and other cloud products will react during and after the reboot. Want to know how your server will react to a reboot? There&amp;rsquo;s no better way to get that answer than to just try it out and see. Of course we recommend doing any testing during the development phase, or on separate servers to limit any customer impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_6&#34;&gt;Mitigating Reboot Impact&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Horizontal Scaling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the best ways to prevent prolonged impact from a reboot is to distribute your application over multiple redundant, tiered, servers. We call this &amp;ldquo;Horizontal Scaling,&amp;rdquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s a great way to minimize the risk of downtime due to any single server going down. There&amp;rsquo;s a very good &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rackspace.com/blog/examining-horizontal-scaling-google-hangout-recap/&#34;&gt;discussion of Horizontal Scaling&lt;/a&gt; in one of the Rackspace Office Hours Hangouts I host.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Custom Error Pages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One benefit of using a Cloud Load Balancer is the ability to set a custom error page in the event that a server connected to the Load Balancer is offline or unresponsive. By proactively configuring that error page, a visitor to your site will receive an error message designed by you, specific to your unique application. Custom Error Pages can be configured via the &lt;a href=&#34;http://docs.rackspace.com/loadbalancers/api/v1.0/clb-devguide/content/Erropage-d1e666.html&#34;&gt;API&lt;/a&gt; or the &lt;a href=&#34;/products/f/25/t/3612&#34;&gt;Control Pane&lt;/a&gt;l.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a Community Manager</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/communitymanager.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/communitymanager.html</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Next week I transition to my second job at Rackspace, a Technical Community Manager. I&amp;rsquo;m very excited, since this role will allow me to spend more of my time extending one-to-many support. I think that my strengths lie in expanding individual support interactions for broader consumption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll be working in our Community Forums and answering as many questions as I can and then looping in other teams for help as needed. I get to work with many additional teams, learning more with each interaction. I&amp;rsquo;ll also be able to work toward my goal of more consistently representing Rackspace and sharing our vision of the future of cloud computing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep Peddling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/keeppeddling.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/keeppeddling.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;img-responsive&#34; src=&#34;//drops.albush.com/keeppeddling.gif&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My four year old son has his first bike. I&amp;rsquo;ve been spending my evenings teaching him how to ride - he&amp;rsquo;s catching on fast. One area he&amp;rsquo;s struggling in is the turns. He&amp;rsquo;s not confident, or not focused, and he tips over in the turns. I was jogging after him, shouting advice, when I realized my advice has implications far beyond beginners cycling - keep peddling and look where you want to be. Whatever twists and turns life throws your way, you can better navigate them if you keep peddling and look where you want to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Keep peddling&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bicycle is an absurd device. Tell a person who has never seen one in action that a human can sit on top of two impossibly thin wheels and balance, and they&amp;rsquo;ll think you&amp;rsquo;re crazy. But bicycles work because of momentum and inertia - and you build those by peddling. My son&amp;rsquo;s problem was that he would slow down in the turns. So much so that he would lose the momentum that kept him upright. He had a few falls, nothing bad, but now is more confident in peddling through the turns so that he keeps his momentum up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When life makes us turn, we sometimes end up slowing down to the point of losing our balance. Should we be cautious? Yes. Should we make sure we understand our surroundings? Yes. But once we know where we&amp;rsquo;re going, we need to pedal fast enough to keep our momentum. Peddling is your key to momentum - and momentum will keep you upright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Look where you want to be; not where you are&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second problem my son faced was not looking where he wanted to be. He would come to an obstacle - a parked car, a trashcan, a street sign - and he would focus on the obstacle, not his path around the obstacle. When he took his eyes off of his path, he lost his balance and tipped over. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to get caught up looking at the scary things in our path. They&amp;rsquo;re large, they are dangerous, and they force us to change our path - all scary things that can grab our attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keeping our eyes on the goal helps us avoid losing our balance. We remember &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; we are heading toward our destination.  Focusing on the goal provides motivation to keep peddling, too, and we can always use that.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Customer Isn&#39;t Always Right</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/customerright.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/customerright.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago I participated in a round of interviews for an open position on our Customer Success Team. I conducted my portion of the interview with my teammate Bill. I always like listening to Bill - he has wonderful insights, and asks great questions. I truly appreciated one question he asked in the interview: &amp;ldquo;Is the customer always right?&amp;rdquo; Fortunately, not one of the candidates answered &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wait - What?&lt;/strong&gt; You work for a company dedicated to supporting the cusotmer - why would you say that the customer isn&amp;rsquo;t always right?&lt;br /&gt;
Because they aren&amp;rsquo;t, and that saying is stupid, anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the customer was always right, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have a job. Fortunately, they&amp;rsquo;re often wrong. Specifically, we&amp;rsquo;re asking the customer the wrong questions. In customer support, we attempt to solve problems as quickly as possible, without making sure that we&amp;rsquo;re answering the real problem. - We end up with the right answer to the wrong question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;What Does Success Look Like?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the primary difference between &lt;em&gt;Customer Support&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Customer Success:&lt;/em&gt; Customer Success seeks to provide long-term, proactive guidance, while Customer Support is focused exclusively on answering the immediate question. Customer Support is &lt;em&gt;Transactional&lt;/em&gt;; Customer Success is &lt;em&gt;Proactive.&lt;/em&gt; Is customer support wrong? No. We need problem solvers.
Forget the immediate question. Go straight to the real question: &amp;ldquo;What does success look like?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Songza Adds Context to Google Play Music</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/context.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/context.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Hey, did you hear that Google is buying music curated music app &lt;a href=&#34;http://songza.com/&#34;&gt;Songza&lt;/a&gt;? I&amp;rsquo;m  very excited about this acquisition. Songza is a bit different than other streaming music apps, in that their playlists are carefully curated around context - What time of day are you listening? What&amp;rsquo;s your mood? What activity are you participating in? - and then plays music based on that context. And I hope that Google will integrate this context directly into their own streaming music app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google is already so good at context - Google Now proves this every day. But their music streaming app could really benefit from some additional contextual help. Play Music already has great music discovery features, including an &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m feeling lucky&amp;rdquo; radio feature which plays a random playlist based on your previous listening habits. While they make good suggestions based on what I&amp;rsquo;ve already listened to, the service does miss out on context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why&lt;/em&gt; I listen, not &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt; I listen to.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One great example of this need for more context is on display when my auto-generated playlists are influenced by one of my most listened to playlists: lullabies for my son. We listen to these each night as we get ready for bed, and I play this playlist from my Google Music account. This influences Google&amp;rsquo;s algorithm, and later the music Google will recommend for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With just a little bit of context - &amp;ldquo;hey, Alan, &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; are you listening to that song?&amp;rdquo; Google would be able to craft much better playlists - and I think that&amp;rsquo;s exactly why they are investing in Songza.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Context is a two-way (or more) street.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other interesting angle of this acquisition is that Google will now get to push context to Songza. Currently, Songza gives you some interesting, time-bound playlist choices. For example, at 12:30 on Wednesday afternoon, Gave me these options:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brand New Music&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boosting Your Energy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working in an Office (SFW)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working (No Lyrics)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Going to a Festival&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Four of those options are pretty good guesses for any old Wednesday afternoon - but what if I work nights? What if I work outside, not in an office? What if I were, actually, going to a specific festival? By integrating with Google, Songza will have a much better idea of what I usually do, where I&amp;rsquo;m going and if I&amp;rsquo;m usually awake at this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that Songza is perfect for Google, and Google is perfect for Songza. I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to seeing how this merger changes everything.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Brewed Benchmarks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/coldbrew.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/coldbrew.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Last week I read an article on Lifehacker about &lt;a href=&#34;http://lifehacker.com/this-cheap-no-mess-cold-brew-system-offers-a-hassle-fr-1582395519&#34;&gt;a less messy way to cold brew coffee&lt;/a&gt;. As a fan of cold brewed coffee, wanted to try this. Cold brewing is very easy, but it does leave a bit of a mess. I needed to be able to brew my coffee quickly, easily and with as little mess as possible.&lt;br /&gt;
The Lifehacker article describes what appears to be a very simple, no cleanup version of the cold brewing process with little to no filtering needed. - that&amp;rsquo;s my Holy Grail, to be able to go straight from brewing to drinking without having to filter. I&amp;rsquo;m not there yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried the method, and it worked, somewhat.  I still had way too much sediment that escaped the bag - I needed to filter the coffee before it was fit to drink. But I ended up with a passable result. And, now I have a solid benchmark to point back to as I adjust more variables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After making my first batch of coffee, I co-hosted a &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zhi8E15_yEQ&amp;amp;amp;feature=share&#34;&gt;live Google Plus Hangout about benchmarking cloud applications&lt;/a&gt;. It was a great reminder that all I had done was fool around with my coffee routine. I had no way to actually generate a baseline from which I could iterate. So this time I went back and made some notes. Now we&amp;rsquo;ll keep adding to this and see how I progress from there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Benchmarks&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
&lt;colgroup&gt;
&lt;col style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;/&gt;
&lt;col style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/colgroup&gt;

&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;Version 1&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;Version 2&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;

&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coffee&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;200g&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;100g&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;1600g&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;500g&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Primary Filter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;Single Filter Bag&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;Single Filter Bag&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grind&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;Coarsest grind on burr grinder&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;Very coarse (blade grinder; pulsed)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outcome&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;too much sediment. Needed much extra filtering.&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left;&#34;&gt;Some sediment, very concentrated flavor&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/helloworld.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/helloworld.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;The part where I welcome you to version X.Y of my blog.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Where &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Y&amp;rdquo; are numbers larger than I would like to admit.&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s just call it iteration number ten. I&amp;rsquo;ve built this blog on the Pelican Framework, with a large dose of help from &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.onitato.com/no-hassle-blog-automation.html&#34;&gt;Justin Phelp&amp;rsquo;s two&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.onitato.com/no-hassle-blog-automation-redux.html&#34;&gt;guides to blog automation&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.getpelican.com/&#34;&gt;Pelican&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Why Pelican?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to build a simple, static site that I can post directly as HTML - either through my own server, or on a Rackspace Cloud Files Container. (That&amp;rsquo;s where we are now.) I also wanted to keep the actual authoring component in-line with my current workflow. I write anything that needs formatting in Markdown, and I like to keep notes in nvALT - which works extremely well with Markdown. I want to be able to quickly move from a note, to a draft, to a live post. Pelican fits that bill. (See what I did there?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;Additional Modifications&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pelican is configured out of the box to work as a dead-simple blog. You write a post in the content folder, then Pelican generates the static files for you - and index page with your latest posts listed, and those individual post pages. But I wanted something which would offer me the option to add an entire static site in front of the blog. And that&amp;rsquo;s easy enough to do with Pelican.&lt;br /&gt;
After a bit of Googling, I found a very useful comment outlining &lt;a href=&#34;http://stackful-dev.com/static-site-jinja-pelican-shared-templates.html#comment-901669793&#34;&gt;how to build a static site with a blog in a subfolder with Pelican&lt;/a&gt;. This allowed me to put up a static shell, and then add my blog posts at ambush.com/blog. Anything I want to keep in the forefront, I&amp;rsquo;ll share as a static page.&lt;br /&gt;
I also wanted to move away from the standard theme, and I&amp;rsquo;d already built a simple, one-page site with bootstrap, so I grabbed the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/DandyDev/pelican-bootstrap3&#34;&gt;Pelican-Bootstrap3 template&lt;/a&gt;, which allowed me to add in my own style changes to match my existing blog. I&amp;rsquo;ve essentially just added a /blog folder, and greatly enhanced my ability to quickly add additional pages and content. Its a great improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_4&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s Next?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who knows? If history is any indication, probably four or five more blog posts, and then a brief break, followed by a slower release of helpful posts. I&amp;rsquo;m also working to import some of my better content from my previous blog iterations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Redis Hangout</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/redishangout.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/redishangout.html</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Every week I host a live video hangout series called &lt;a href=&#34;http://go.rackspace.com/officehours&#34;&gt;Office Hours&lt;/a&gt;. We discuss a range of cloud computing topics, and invite guest experts in to share their experience. This past week I had the honor of chatting with three members of the Rackspace Data Stores team about Redis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;video-container&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/-eIxC7oF4Ic?feature=player_embedded&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Highlights&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What are some good use cases for Redis that aren&amp;rsquo;t readily obvious?

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://youtu.be/-eIxC7oF4Ic?t=6m28s&#34;&gt;Tracking stats/metrics/processing logs - Because redid is all in memory, it&amp;rsquo;s great for processing metrics.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://youtu.be/-eIxC7oF4Ic?t=8m37s&#34;&gt;Using Redis as a queue or buffer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Does Redis just replace mySQL?

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redis can augment mySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://youtu.be/-eIxC7oF4Ic?t=23m24s&#34;&gt;Redis can work well with nginx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://youtu.be/-eIxC7oF4Ic?t=26m7s&#34;&gt;How can you implement Redis?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://youtu.be/-eIxC7oF4Ic?t=31m4s&#34;&gt;Advice on starting with Redis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://youtu.be/-eIxC7oF4Ic?t=43m37s&#34;&gt;Real life examples of successful Redis implementations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>